<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SearchIndexes Version="1.0">
    <Documents>
        <Document ID="3">
            <Title>Darkness</Title>
            <Text>General info


Name
Darkness (The Dark, Oblivion Queen, Eternal Shadow)
Gender
None, but take a female form
Age
Eternal
Race
DarkSpawn
Role
Antagonist


Physical Description


Eyes
Red
Hair
Snow and Ashes
Skin
Stone Grey
Build
Voluptuous
Height
na
Weight
na
Scars etc
na


Personality

Cruel
Manipulative
Sadist
Childish
Egoist
Scorned


Relationships to other Characters

Sister to Lightness
Mother to Darkon, Tenerion, Obscurio

Others

Discovering about existing and being with her sister, she betrayed and stabbed her when learning Lightness was able to leave the nothing and mingle with the worlds around. She spent eternity from there on chasing her sister “soul” to finally destroy it</Text>
            <Notes>￼</Notes>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="4">
            <Title>Characters</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="5">
            <Title>Characters</Title>
            <Text>General info


Name

Gender

Age

Race

Role



Physical Description


Eyes

Hair

Skin

Build

Height

Weight

Scars etc



Personality



Relationships to other Characters



Others

</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="6">
            <Title>Templates</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="7">
            <Title>Images</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="8">
            <Title>Place</Title>
            <Text>Name



Description


Images references</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="9">
            <Title>Plots</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="10">
            <Title>Events</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="11">
            <Title>Event</Title>
            <Text>What



When



Where



Who



Why


</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="12">
            <Title>Plot</Title>
            <Text>What





Who



</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="13">
            <Title>Darkon</Title>
            <Synopsis>Darkness second son, put in charge of capturing the soul of Lightness</Synopsis>
            <Text>General info


Name
Darkon
Gender
Male
Age
unknown
Race
Fallen Angel (in truth, unknown)
Role
Fake-Antagonist



Physical Description


Eyes
Dark blue
Hair
silver
Skin
Fair tanned
Build
Muscled-Lean
Height
1m90
Weight

Scars etc



Personality

Cynic
Jealous
Manipulative
Confident
Charmer

Relationships to other Characters					

Boyfriend to Fel
Second son of Darkness
Two brothers: Obscurio and Tenerion

Others

Believe himself incapable of feelings beyond surface ones</Text>
            <Notes>￼</Notes>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="14">
            <Title>Felina</Title>
            <Synopsis>Main character</Synopsis>
            <Text>General info


Name
Felina Faerlain
Gender
Female
Age
23
Race
Human
Role
Protagonist


Physical Description


Eyes
Jade
Hair
Copper Blond
Skin
Fair
Build
Average
Height
1m70
Weight

Scars etc



Personality

Kind, cheerful and open minded.
Prompt to panic, tend to over-react
Oblivious about feelings
Quick to superficial anger

Relationships to other Characters

Family of four:
Mother
Father
Sister
Girlfriend of Darkon
Soul-twin of Fera


Others

Work at the Martyr’s bar as maid
Is the accidental receptacle of Lightness’s soul</Text>
            <Notes>Nicknamed Fel by her friends</Notes>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="15">
            <Title>Darkon pinup</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="16">
            <Title>Darkon/Fel</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="17">
            <Title>Saig</Title>
            <Synopsis>Celtic Vampire
Martyr'</Synopsis>
            <Text>General info


Name
Saig (son of Aed)
Gender
Male
Age
2259(born around 246 BC)(21y old when turned)
Race
Vampire (born human)
Role
Major character


Physical Description


Eyes
Granit Grey
Hair
Plasma Blue
Skin
White
Build
Lean, on the side of thin
Height
1m83
Weight

Scars etc
A carved rune below his left ribs (R upside-down)


Personality

Playful
Teasing
Obnoxious
Masochist
Private with feelings

Relationships to other Characters

Occasional shag-buddy to Damien
Friend to Fel
Owned by Darkon
Ex-lover of Myriam

Others

Work as host at the Martyr’s bar</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="18">
            <Title>General Setting</Title>
            <Synopsis>Modern Day Paris
2013 story start</Synopsis>
            <Text>Fel Story start 2013, Fel is then 23</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="19">
            <Title>Races</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="20">
            <Title>darkness</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="21">
            <Title>Vampire</Title>
            <Text>Origins

The first tribes of humans that walked the earth in prehistoric times often fought, over territories, hunting grounds etc, even among themselves when time were harsh.
In one of those tribes lived two brothers (Cain and Abel), and during a period of famine they fought over whatever food they had left for their own survival.
One of them was killed in the scuffle but a demon that passed by took interest in the conflict. He offered the dying human a unique possibilities. A contract, a deal, that would bring him back from the dead but with consequences.
Abel seized this last chance, not caring that the demon never mentioned a price.
He woke up with no heartbeat, no breath, and an unending thirst for blood.

He lived first for years, hidden away in fear of what he became, committing murders or massacre on whoever or whatever crossed his path.
He eventually learned (alone) to control himself.
Years more he meddled with humans alone, and finally succumbed to the temptation of having another like him to alleviate loneliness.
He created himself a mate, then a son…

He kept a tight leash on them, until a fight had them separate. They created more, and so did he, keeping to the rule of being hidden, trying to remain a secret, and peaceful (as much as could be) race.
Nowadays about 0.01% of the world population belong to them (about seven hundred thousands people).




Social Organization
Vampires have a very strict if very simple social structure.
They belong to and depend of the vampire who made them.
Newly created Vampires nowadays are considered ruffian, of low “birth”
The older a vampire is, the more power and rank they gives to their “children”
They call their ranks “Sons”, “Daughters” or “Generations” (Abel is the first Generation, the Father. The “First sons” are by extension “Second Generation”)

A vampire can command and order any other vampire below them, and lower ranked vampires are often used as body guards, hunters, domestics, by higher ranked
A vampire can challenge their “sire” in a fight which must happen with witnesses. The rules and wager of the fight must be defined in front of the same witnesses.
Very often it’s a fight to the death and by removing their “Sire” the vampire (and all others of their rank) climb up a “Generation”


Creation

Creating a vampire is a painful process on both the vampire and the being that turns.
The vampire must first drink the blood of their victim until they are nearing death. Until that is done, not a drop of vampire blood must enter their body, else the process can be unstable and has greater chances to fail.

Once the victim is nearly dead, the vampire must feed their own blood back (which imply being well fed in the first place) to them.
When the victim has absorbed enough blood (the eyes are the first to change, and used to recognize the start of the transformation) the vampire need to finish them off and drink all the life they have left
The human body has a very small chance of rejecting the transformation and dying for real (around 0.001%)

The whole thing doesn’t necessarily take long, but it’s exhausting on both side.

If the victim has already consumed vampire blood in the last forty-eight hours, there is a risk of instability and his body, which increase the chances of reject. The more blood consumed and the more recent it was, the more risk there is.

Feeding habits

Vampires need blood to live. Human blood isn’t a must and all bloods give off different amount of energy but it’s mostly simply a matter of ease. There is many more humans on the planet than anything else, it’s easier to go after them (easy preys) and drinking can be coupled with other activities.
The sensation of power held over another sentient specie is also a great appeal to vampires

They feed thanks to their fangs (a deformation of their canine) by biting deeply enough any point on their victim. Once the wound is open, they simply suck the life liquid and drink it.
The bite is usually painful (as bites tend to be) unless the vampire apply his own blood on it. The “vampire contaminant” of it induce a “high” in the victim, act as an anesthetic and help close the wound
</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="22">
            <Title>Demon</Title>
            <Text>Origins

Origins of the first demons are rather vague and few, it’s often mentioned that they came to be from drop of darkness fallen hellfire in a plain where time was out of sync. As poetic as this is, the more realistic explanation is that indeed a drop of pure liquid void fell into a flame and the resulting explosion deformed and contaminated other creatures around it and the world itself. The demon realm thus became a plane all on its own but dependent of the main world and closely linked to it.


Sub-Races

Demons is the main denomination, but among themselves they have many sub-races (incubus/succubus, imps, etc)
Every demon when they come into existence, see a “birthmark” appear somewhere on their skin. It’s a brand and it indicate their sub-race. The mark is a circle, broken in seven pieces, with a flame in the middle.
Each segment correspond to a sub-race, and one (or more) of them will take a triangle shape, indicating the demon sub-race.

Pure-blooded normally have all the triangles-segments, making nearly all noble demons think they’re a separate race.
Opposite to them, contracted have no triangle. And the same thinking applies.


Social Organization

Demons are organized depending on their age, and their bloodline. Since a diluted bloodline means diluted powers they attach a lot of importance to their parentage.
Their society is a monarchy in name, a tyranny in facts. The king/queen is the from the oldest and purest family of demons that exist, and S/he is sitting on the throne only as long as her/is siblings or children don’t forcefully get her/im off it.

The court is composed of all the other families and often the theater of tragedies and betrayals aplenty. Nobles are not required to work, but it’s very encourage to get into contract with humans to obtain their life force and increase their energy and their strength.

Demons born from a contract (and so who were humans) are the lowest of the low. They’re considered the property of their contractor. (slavery)


Creation

A demon can be created by three different manners:

A drop of darkness fallen in hellfire. As the old poesy goes, a demon can spontaneously come into existence if a drop of liquid void come into contact with hellfire and mix in a stable manner. (very very rare. The rest of the time such reaction is more along the lines of “Boom”)
Procreation. A male and female (as a general rules, demons can be bi-gendered or switch physically) get together and get a baby demon. Nothing too complicated
Contract. A human who make a deal with a demon and at the end of their deal, their soul is twisted into a weakened, very diluted version of the demon that contracted them.

</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="23">
            <Title>Angel</Title>
            <Text>Origins





Social Organization



Creation</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="24">
            <Title>Elf</Title>
            <Text>Origins





Social Organization



Creation</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="25">
            <Title>Human</Title>
            <Text>Most numerous race in the world
Cover all the planet, very diversified

All of their myths are based on the lies or distorted stories about other kinds around

See human race nowadays</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="26">
            <Title>Places</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="27">
            <Title>Damien</Title>
            <Text>General info


Name
Damien Son of Eklaid
Gender
Male (Female for two years but didn’t like it cf society)
Age

Race
Demon
Role
Major Character


Physical Description


Eyes
Bright Day Sky Blue
Hair
Fire Orange
Skin
Olive
Build
Lean muscled
Height
1m84
Weight

Scars etc
Demon Birthmark between the shoulderblades: a circle cut in seven segments-triangles, with a stylized flame in the middle


Personality

Playful
Teasing
Charmer
Impulsive
Childish

Relationships to other Characters

Occasional shag-buddy to Saig
Cousin to Deerck
Brother to the current King of the nether realm
Friend to Fel
Owned by Darkon

Others

Work as host at the Martyr’s Bar
Considered inexistant by his father all his childhood, he is deeply traumatized at the idea of being ignored</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="28">
            <Title>Saig pinup</Title>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="29">
            <Title>Deerck</Title>
            <Text>General info


Name
Deerck (humans often call him Dereck)Son of Giral
Gender
Male
Age

Race
Demon
Role
Major Character


Physical Description


Eyes
Dandelion yellow
Hair
Coal black
Skin
Olive
Build
Muscled
Height
1m87
Weight

Scars etc
Demon Birthmark on his back, above the right hip: a circle cut in seven segments, the upper one a triangle, with a stylized flame in the middle


Personality

Calm and well mannered
Prideful
Silent
Determined
Manipulative

Relationships to other Characters

Cousin of Damien


Others

Born from a demon father and a human mother
Host and Barman of the Marty’s Bar
Ranked noble through vicious and shady political moves
Consider it his life goal to protect and keep Damien alive</Text>
        </Document>
        <Document ID="30">
            <Title>Sylvain</Title>
            <Text>General info


Name
Sylvain Of Emerely
Gender
Male
Age
735(born in 1278)
Race
Elf
Role
Major Character


Physical Description


Eyes
Amethyst
Hair
Kobicha
Skin
Pale golden
Build
Lean muscled
Height
1m86
Weight

Scars etc
Serrated scar on his left thigh, whip marks on his back, several “small” cuts around his upper arms, chaffing and burn scars on his lower legs


Personality

Silent
Manipulative
Cold-blooded killer
Very good at pretend, often appear cheerful and kind

Relationships to other Characters

Owned by Darkon
Brother to Ophiriel
Son of Eldiarion

Others

Nearly no morals whatsoever due to the loss of his sister when young, he consider everything is fair game to reach whatever goals he has. Except rape. He abhor rape and will destroy anyone he knows who commit such a crime.</Text>
        </Document>
    </Documents>
</SearchIndexes>
